



#### **Contacts**



kubajarecki1205@gmail.com



+46 722 58 38 99 +48 606 341 688



Forvägen 1, lgh 1002 145 51 Norsborg Stockholm, Sweden

#### **Education**

2022: Skylift Course.

2020: Safety at Work course.

2017-2020: Elektrikergymnasiet.

2014-2017: Kunskapsskolan.

2007-2014: Tallidsskolan.

## Languages

Swedish: Fluently English: Fluently

Polish: Native language

Russian: Basic

# **About Me**

I am a 21 year old (*Birthdate: 2001-05-12*) electrician and most of my work experience lies in the car charging industry. I studied at Elektrikergymnasiet - a school reserved exclusively for future electricians. There I learnt both electricity and electronics, safety during work, as well as some industrial electricity.

In my life I had the opportunity to understand how important psychological well-being is at work and everywhere else. Therefore I do what I can to make sure that everyone in my team feels important and understood, which boosts efficiency and prevents burning out.

I also enjoy working in a well planned and methodical way. I happily take part in planning, follow the plan and learn as much as possible while cooperating with my team whether I am the one following commands or the one taking lead.

Character traits: Responsible, learns easily, enjoy to learn from

others, like to do things to the point where I'm proud

of my work.

Interests: Playing instruments, skiing, fauna, psychology,

electricity. It's really easier to list things I'm not

interested in.

Citizenship: Swedish and Polish.

## **Working Experience**

2022-2023 – Electrician and larm technician at **Burtec**.

I installed burglar alarm systems in very high-security places, like large hospitals, laboratories and server rooms. I also did electrical work that includes renovating the electrical part of old, delicate and exclusive apartments and offices.

2019 to 2022 - Electrician at NewEL.

I installed car chargers (hardware, software, network, heavy cables, electrical assemblies, load balancers) for organisations and private people. I also did smart house systems and LED lighting, both outdoor and indoor.

2018 - Summer-work at Subtopia.

I organised activities for children, took care of food for them and did some documentation.

*2017 - Distribution of advertisement for Tommys Fönsterputs.* 

I physically drove around Stockholm distributing ads for a window cleaning

company. Learned to plan work and route effectively.

References available upon request.